Guide to the Kevin Killian and Dodie Bellamy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1965-2012; Series VI; 13.3; (24 boxes)
  - 8x10 Photographs, 1965-2012
    - Kobe Leah, "Too Far" collaboration with Kevin Killian, undated (Box 67)
    - Mark Leckey, undated (Box 67)
    - Neil LeDoux, undated (Box 67)
    - LeDoux Road (Los Angeles), undated (Box 67)
    - 11 Lee, undated (Box 67)
    - Matty Lee, undated (Box 67)
    - Tim Lee, undated (Box 67)
    - Charles Legere, undated (Box 67)
    - Lego car on Natoma Street, 2006 (Box 67)
    - Ace Lehner, undated (Box 67)
    - Andrew Leland, undated (Box 67)
    - Timm Lenk, undated (Box 67)
    - Lenox Hotel light fixture, undated (Box 67)
    - Ben Lerner, undated (Box 67)
    - Sharon Lerner, undated (Box 67)
    - Gabriel Lester, undated (Box 67)
    - Dennis Letbetter, undated (Box 67)
    - Jonathan Lethem, undated (Box 67)
    - Tony Leuzzi, undated (Box 67)
    - Lever Brothers John and Nathen, undated (Box 67)
    - Jennifer Burns Levin, undated (Box 67)
    - Philip Levine, undated (Box 67)
    - Stacey Levine, undated (Box 67)
    - Rachel Levitsky, undated (Box 67)
    - Andrew Levy, undated (Box 67)
    - Walter K. Lew, undated (Box 67)
    - Ali Liebegott, undated (Box 67)
    - Joe Licht as "Lee" in Erling Wold's opera Queer, undated (Box 67)
    - Liliane Lijn, undated (Box 67)
    - Tao Lin, undated (Box 67)
    - Bob Linder, undated (Box 67)
    - Edward Lindquist, undated (Box 67)
    - Mark Linenthal, undated (Box 67)
    - Alphonso Lingis, undated (Box 67)
    - R. Zamora Linmark, undated (Box 67)
    - Beth Lisick, undated (Box 67)
    - Paul Lisicky, undated (Box 67)
    - Liste 07, Basel, June 2007, 2007 June (Box 67)
    - Ira Livingston, undated (Box 67)
    - Jennifer Locke, undated (Box 67)
    - Tamara Loewinstein, undated (Box 67)
    - Sam Lohmann, undated (Box 67)
    - Lonely Christopher, undated (Box 67)
    - Gareth Long, undated (Box 67)
    - Meric Long, undated (Box 67)
    - Catherine Lord and Kaucilya Brooke, undated (Box 67)
    - Sylvere Lotringer, undated (Box 67)
    - Brendan Lott, undated (Box 67)
    - Michael Lowenthal, undated (Box 74)
    - Alvin Lu, undated (Box 67)
    - Jacqueline E. Luckett, 2012 spelling bee champ (Box 67)
    - Roman Lujan, undated (Box 67)
    - Attila Richard Lukacs, undated (Box 67)
    - Michael David Lukas, undated (Box 67)
    - Ken Lum, undated (Box 67)
    - Francois Luong, undated (Box 67)
    - Christopher Lura, undated (Box 67)
    - Dorothy Trujillo Lusk, undated (Box 67)
    - Luther Price, "A" (screenshot), undated (Box 67)
    - Dietmar Lutz "Bird," in Kata's pad, undated (Box 67)
    - Leora Lutz, undated (Box 67)
    - Erick Lyle, undated (Box 67)
    - Kimberly Lyons with Jasper Johns print, undated (Box 67)
    - Jason McBride, undated (Box 67)
    - Susan McCabe, undated (Box 67)
    - Steve Mccaffrey, undated (Box 67)
    - Richard McCann, undated (Box 67)
    - Paul McCarthy, undated (Box 67)
    - Alistair McCartney, undated (Box 74)
    - Michael McClure, undated (Box 67)
    - David McConnell, undated (Box 67)
    - Derek McCormack, undated (Box 67)
    - Derek Jason, undated (Box 67)
    - Phillip McCrum, undated (Box 67)
    - Euan McDonald, undated (Box 67)
    - Tara McDowell, undated (Box 67)
    - Michael Magee, undated (Box 67)
    - Adam McEwen, undated (Box 67)
    - Sean McFarland, undated (Box 67)
    - Ryan McGinley, undated (Box 67)
    - Anne McGuire, undated (Box 67)
    - Anne McGuire and Martha Colburn, undated (Box 67)
    - Keegan McHargue, undated (Box 67)
    - Keegan McHargue and Bruce Conner, undated (Box 67)
    - Dan Machlin, undated (Box 67)
    - Walter Maciel, undated (Box 67)
    - Meg Mack, undated (Box 67)
    - Donna McKechnie, undated (Box 67)
    - Kristine McKenna, undated (Box 67)
    - Nate Mackey, undated (Box 67)
    - Casey McKinney's sweater, undated (Box 67)
    - Graham Mackintosh, undated (Box 67)
    - Malcolm Mclaren (with Michele di Menna, Ryan Siegan-Smith, Kristoffer Frick, Maria von Hausswolff), undated (Box 67)
    - Scott Macleod, undated (Box 67)
    - Jackson Mac Low, undated (Box 74)
    - Christina McPhee, undated (Box 67)
    - Mickey Mahoney, undated (Box 67)
    - Thomas Main, pants pulled down, undated (Box 67)
    - Thomas Main in a jockstrap, undated (Box 67)
    - Raimundas Malasauskas, undated (Box 67)
    - Elyse Mallouk, undated (Box 68)
    - Donato Mancini, undated (Box 68)
    - Donato Mancini and Jordan Scott, undated (Box 68)
    - Donato Mancini, Guinevere Pencarrick, Jamie Reid, undated (Box 68)
    - Mark Manders, undated (Box 68)
    - Andrew Mania, undated (Box 68)
    - Randall Mann, undated (Box 68)
    - Peter Maravelis, undated (Box 68)
    - Anthony Marcellini, undated (Box 68)
    - Leigh Marcopoulos, undated (Box 68)
    - Ben Marcus, undated (Box 68)
    - Greil Marcus, undated (Box 68)
    - Mariana, and Yoshua Okon, undated (Box 68)
    - Mariana Camouflage, undated (Box 68)
    - Filip Marinovich, undated (Box 68)
    - Suzi Markham at her wedding, undated (Box 68)
    - Daphne Marlatt, undated (Box 68)
    - Regina Marler, undated (Box 68)
    - D.S. Marriott, undated (Box 68)
    - D.S. Marriott and Anselm Berrigan, undated (Box 68)
    - Chris Martin, undated (Box 68)
    - Chris Martin and Dodie Bellamy, undated (Box 68)
    - CJ Martin, undated (Box 68)
    - Daria Martin, undated (Box 68)
    - Douglas A. Martin, undated (Box 68)
    - Douglas A. Martin, undated (Box 68)
    - Kris Martin, undated (Box 68)
    - MG "Matt" Martin, undated (Box 68)
    - Masha, the daughter of Kota and Katya, undated (Box 68)
    - Blair Mastbaum, undated (Box 68)
    - John Mateer, undated (Box 68)
    - Travis Mathews, undated (Box 68)
    - Lydia Matthews and Rigo 06, undated (Box 68)
    - Armistead Maupin, undated (Box 74)
    - Rolf Maurer, undated (Box 68)
    - Bernadette Mayer, undated (Box 68)
    - Keith Mayerson, undated (Box 68)
    - Tom Mayock, the Lew Welch Guy, undated (Box 68)
    - Ben Mazer, undated (Box 68)
    - Taylor Mead, undated (Box 68)
    - Jason Meadows, undated (Box 68)
    - Jason Meder, undated (Box 68)
    - Cheryl Meeker, undated (Box 68)
    - James Meetze, undated (Box 68)
    - Todd Melick, undated (Box 68)
    - Bernadine Mellis and Andrea Lawlor, undated (Box 68)
    - David Melnick, undated (Box 68)
    - Mark Mendoza, undated (Box 68)
    - David Menendez Alvarez, undated (Box 68)
    - W. S. Merwin, undated (Box 68)
    - JL ("Joanne") Meyer, undated (Box 68)
    - Peter Middleton, undated (Box 68)
    - Roy Miki, undated (Box 68)
    - Harvey Milk suit, undated (Box 68)
    - Billy Miller, undated (Box 68)
    - J. Hillis Miller, undated (Box 68)
    - Michael Miller, undated (Box 68)
    - Rebecca Miller, undated (Box 68)
    - Susan Miller, undated (Box 68)
    - Tim Miller, at home with Shakespeare doll, undated (Box 68)
    - Drew Milne, undated (Box 68)
    - Karla Milosevich, undated (Box 68)
    - Mina, the daughter of Brent and Melissa, undated (Box 68)
    - Carrie Minikin, undated (Box 68)
    - Chelsey Minnis, undated (Box 68)
    - Carol Mirakove, undated (Box 68)
    - Mirror Scene from "Too Far", undated (Box 68)
    - Rumi Missabu of the Cockettes, undated (Box 68)
    - Attractive Mission Street building, undated (Box 68)
    - Peter and Caitlin Mitchell-Dayton, undated (Box 68)
    - MLA Convention hotel lobby, J W Marriott downtown LA, undated (Box 68)
    - Chuck Mobley, undated (Box 68)
    - Moby Dick show at Wattis Institute, October 2009, 2009 October (Box 68)
    - K. Silem Mohammad, undated (Box 68)
    - Bill Mohr, undated (Box 68)
    - Roy Molinari, the face of evil, undated (Box 68)
    - Michael Montlack, undated (Box 68)
    - Moon souvenir from "The Maidens" and from the estate of Robin Blaser, undated (Box 68)
    - Candace Moore, undated (Box 68)
    - Richard O. Moore, undated (Box 68)
    - Thurston Moore, undated (Box 68)
    - Thurston Moore and Dodie Bellamy, undated (Box 68)
    - Julio Cesar -Morales, undated (Box 68)
    - Bruna Mori, undated (Box 68)
    - David Morini, undated (Box 68)
    - Erin Morrill, undated (Box 68)
    - Dee Morris, undated (Box 68)
    - Jason Morris, undated (Box 68)
    - Marianne Morris, undated (Box 68)
    - Michael Morris, undated (Box 68)
    - Tracie Morris, undated (Box 68)
    - Rusty Morrison, undated (Box 68)
    - Yedda Morrison, undated (Box 74)
    - Jesse Morse, undated (Box 68)
    - Anna Moschovakis, undated (Box 68)
    - Joseph Mosconi, undated (Box 68)
    - Donal Mosher, undated (Box 68)
    - Donal Mosher and Christine Shields, undated (Box 68)
    - Kevin with Lisa Motherwell (from LMW listserv), undated (Box 68)
    - Stephen Motika, undated (Box 68)
    - Motoko at Strange Wrinkle opening, undated (Box 68)
    - Jacqueline Motzer, undated (Box 68)
    - Murray Moulding, undated (Box 68)
    - Stephen Mounce, "Babette" from The Joan Jett Blakk Show, undated (Box 68)
    - Jennifer Moxley, undated (Box 68)
    - Paul Muldoon, undated (Box 68)
    - Liz Mulholland, undated (Box 68)
    - Harryette Mullen, undated (Box 68)
    - Dave Muller, undated (Box 68)
    - Student at Stadelschule, Art Basel 2007 (Box 68)
    - Brighde Mullins, undated (Box 68)
    - Ryan Murphy, undated (Box 68)
    - Ben Murray, undated (Box 68)
    - Beth Murray, undated (Box 68)
    - Yxta Maya Murray, undated (Box 68)
    - Museum Cafe, undated (Box 68)
    - Michael Musto, undated (Box 68)
    - My Little Red Book (Vancouver exhibition at "The Apartment"), undated (Box 68)
    - My Own Private Idaho (Portland location), undated (Box 68)
    - Julian Myers, undated (Box 68)
    - Eileen Myles, undated (Box 68)
    - Eileen Myles and Will Alexander, undated (Box 68)
    - Mythos Gallery, undated (Box 68)
    - Sawako Nakayasu, undated (Box 68)
    - Name in Lights, undated (Box 68)
    - Richard Eoin Nash, undated (Box 68)
    - Tenney Nathanson, undated (Box 68)
    - Michael Nava, undated (Box 68)
    - Christopher Nealon, undated (Box 68)
    - Jethro Nededog, undated (Box 68)
    - John Neff, undated (Box 68)
    - Jay Nelson, undated (Box 69)
    - Maggie Nelson, undated (Box 69)
    - Benny Nemerofsky-Ramsey, undated (Box 69)
    - Manuel Neri, undated (Box 69)
    - New Museum on the Bowery, undated (Box 69)
    - Bob Newhart's building from his 70s TV sitcom, undated (Box 69)
    - Julie Newmar, with KK and her son John Smith, undated (Box 69)
    - Ryan Newton, undated (Box 69)
    - Sianne Ngai, undated (Box 69)
    - Niagara Falls, undated (Box 69)
    - Barbara Nicholls, undated (Box 69)
    - Peter Nicholls, undated (Box 69)
    - Jessica Nichols and Michael Slosek, undated (Box 69)
    - Mel Nichols in Vancouver, undated (Box 69)
    - Mel Nichols and Rod Smith, undated (Box 69)
    - Miriam Nichols, undated (Box 69)
    - Andy Nicholson, undated (Box 69)
    - Joel Nickels, undated (Box 69)
    - Daniel Nicoletta, undated (Box 69)
    - Michael Nicoloff, undated (Box 69)
    - Andre Niebuhr, undated (Box 69)
    - Aaron Nielsen and John Waters, undated (Box 69)
    - Angelo Nikolopoulos, undated (Box 69)
    - Jim Nisbet, undated (Box 69)
    - Kevin Nolan, undated (Box 69)
    - Bradford Nordeen, undated (Box 69)
    - Jockum Nordstrom, undated (Box 69)
    - Harold Norse, undated (Box 69)
    - Alice Notley, undated (Box 69)
    - Alex Novik, undated (Box 69)
    - Mark Nowak, undated (Box 69)
    - Raphael Noz, undated (Box 69)
    - Kaya Oakes, undated (Box 69)
    - Odessa Staircase Redux, undated (Box 69)
    - Arthur Okamura, undated (Box 69)
    - Okichuu at Strange Wrinkle opening, undated (Box 69)
    - Yoshua Okon, undated (Box 69)
    - Yoshua Okon and Andrew Berardini, undated (Box 69)
    - Peter O'Leary, undated (Box 69)
    - Ben Olin, UK friend of Paul Foster Johnson, undated (Box 69)
    - Akilah Oliver, undated (Box 69)
    - Michael Oliveras, undated (Box 69)
    - Jenni Olson, undated (Box 69)
    - Michelle O'Marah, undated (Box 69)
    - Michael Ondaatje, undated (Box 69)
    - Hanif O'Neill, undated (Box 69)
    - Jamie O'Neill, undated (Box 69)
    - Opening Night of "Flow Winged Crocodile", undated (Box 69)
    - Opera Singer on Maiden Lane, undated (Box 69)
    - Catherine Opie, undated (Box 69)
    - Linda Oppen, undated (Box 69)
    - Tom Orange, undated (Box 69)
    - Tom Orange and Lynne Dreyer, undated (Box 69)
    - Abe Orden, undated (Box 69)
    - Orgasm by Dodie Bellamy SPT, January 2007, 2007 January (Box 69)
    - Pat O'Riley and Peter Cole, undated (Box 69)
    - Alvin Orloff, undated (Box 69)
    - Genesis P. Orridge, undated (Box 69)
    - Jena Osman, undated (Box 69)
    - Bob Ostertag, undated (Box 69)
    - Tony Oursler, undated (Box 69)
    - Maureen Owen, undated (Box 69)
    - Christopher Owens, undated (Box 69)
    - ZZ Packer, undated (Box 69)
    - Phyllis Pagano and Jane Sylvanus by Dale, undated (Box 69)
    - Chihuly sculpture, spring 2008, 2008 Spring (Box 69)
    - Chuck Palahniuk, undated (Box 69)
    - Michael Palmer, undated (Box 69)
    - Ronald Palmer, undated (Box 69)
    - Michael Palmieri, undated (Box 69)
    - Paper Streamers at Positions Colloquium, August 2008, 2008 August (Box 69)
    - Ethan Paquin, undated (Box 69)
    - Jorge Pardo crib, undated (Box 69)
    - Harry Parker and Caitlin Mitchell, undated (Box 69)
    - Dayton's portrait of him, undated (Box 69)
    - Lara Parker /Lamar Hawkins, undated (Box 69)
    - Parking Meter Flattened, undated (Box 69)
    - Ariel Parkinson, undated (Box 69)
    - Justin Parks as Catherine Deneuve, Buffalo 2009 (Box 69)
    - Richard Parks and Andrew Leland, undated (Box 69)
    - Ian Patrick, undated (Box 69)
    - Julie Patton, undated (Box 69)
    - Molly Peacock, undated (Box 69)
    - Aaron Peck, undated (Box 69)
    - Dale Peck, undated (Box 69)
    - Mitzi Pederson's studio, undated (Box 69)
    - Mitzi Pederson, undated (Box 69)
    - Ted Pelton, undated (Box 69)
    - Edgardo Pena, undated (Box 69)
    - Pencil House photos, undated (Box 69)
    - Brian Pera, undated (Box 69)
    - Bob Perelman leaving SF, 1990 (Box 69)
    - Javier Peres as Martha Stewart, Halloween 2004, 2004 Ocotber 31 (Box 69)
    - Javier Peres, Liste 07, undated (Box 69)
    - Marjorie Perloff, undated (Box 69)
    - Nancy Peters, undated (Box 69)
    - Tim Peterson, undated (Box 69)
    - Simon Pettet, undated (Box 69)
    - Raymond Pettibon, undated (Box 69)
    - Ryan Pierce, undated (Box 69)
    - Pierre et Gilles, undated (Box 74)
    - Ian Phillips, undated (Box 69)
    - Felice Picano, undated (Box 69)
    - Justine Pimlott, undated (Box 69)
    - Pinatas at "The Apartment," Vancouver, September 2010, 2010 September (Box 69)
    - Pink Steam Show, SFPL, July 2004, 2004 July (Box 69)
    - Robert Pinsky, undated (Box 69)
    - Boris Pintar, undated (Box 69)
    - Nick Piombino, undated (Box 69)
    - Job Piston, undated (Box 69)
    - Vanessa Place, undated (Box 69)
    - Plaid picture, undated (Box 69)
    - Lee Plested, undated (Box 69)
    - Kristina Lee Podesva and Jeff Khonsary (of Fillip), undated (Box 69)
    - Poets' Corner at Suzi's wedding (photo by Dodie Bellamy), undated (Box 69)
    - Julian Poirier, undated (Box 69)
    - Scott Polach, undated (Box 69)
    - Michael J. Pollard, undated (Box 69)
    - Genesis Breyer P-Orridge in video, undated (Box 69)
    - Portland Street Corner Labor Day 2005 (Box 69)
    - Matthew Post, undated (Box 69)
    - D.A. Powell, undated (Box 69)
    - Doug Powell, undated (Box 69)
    - Printing Class, UC Berkeley, Fall 2005, 2005 Fall (Box 69)
    - Prop 8 protests, November 2008, 2008 November (Box 69)
    - Rob Pruitt, undated (Box 69)
    - Punctuation Show, Right Window, October 2009, 2009 Ocotber (Box 69)
    - Neighbors' Pumpkin, undated (Box 69)
    - c e putnam, undated (Box 69)
    - Alyssa Quart, undated (Box 69)
    - Meredith Quartermain, undated (Box 69)
    - Rebecca Quaytman (photo by Dodie Bellamy), undated (Box 69)
    - R.H. Quaytman cookies at SFMOMA Cafe, undated (Box 69)
    - Carol Queen, undated (Box 69)
    - Sina Queyras, undated (Box 69)
    - The Quickening by Sue deBeer, January 2007 installation, 2007 January (Box 69)
    - Patty Quill, undated (Box 69)
    - Quincy, undated (Box 69)
    - Quixote puppet, undated (Box 69)
    - Raccoon Eye (photo by Dodie Bellamy), undated (Box 70)
    - Judy Radul, undated (Box 70)
    - Brian Rahm, the boyfriend of my niece, undated (Box 70)
    - Summer, undated (Box 70)
    - Railing outside our door, undated (Box 70)
    - Yvonne Rainer, undated (Box 70)
    - Carl Rakosi, undated (Box 70)
    - Belle Randall, undated (Box 70)
    - Claudia Rankine, undated (Box 70)
    - John Rapko, undated (Box 70)
    - Stephen Ratcliffe, undated (Box 70)
    - Amy Rathbone, undated (Box 70)
    - Robert Rauschenberg's 1953 "Elemental Sculpture", undated (Box 70)
    - Jeremy Ravdin, undated (Box 70)
    - Tom Raworth, undated (Box 70)
    - Rex Ray, undated (Box 70)
    - Rex Ray and Amy Scholder, undated (Box 74)
    - Rex Ray at Visual AIDS sale, undated (Box 70)
    - Oscar Raymundo, undated (Box 70)
    - Red Right Hand class, Halloween 2008, 2008 October 31 (Box 70)
    - Elizabeth Reddin, undated (Box 70)
    - Harry Redl, undated (Box 70)
    - Ishmael Reed, undated (Box 70)
    - Ted Rees' Wojnarowicz tattoo, undated (Box 70)
    - Jennifer Reeves, undated (Box 70)
    - Matthias Regan, undated (Box 70)
    - Rehearsing The Red and the Green at Kota's studio, 2005 (Box 70)
    - Rehearsing Love Can Build a Bridge at Rex's studio, 2009 (Box 70)
    - Rehearsing The Smith Family at Craig's apartment, 2009 (Box 70)
    - Evan Rehill, undated (Box 70)
    - Brett Reichman's diptych, "Time Is/Time Was" (1993) (Box 70)
    - Jamie Reid, undated (Box 70)
    - Laurie Reid and Kevin Killian, photo by Wayne Smith, undated (Box 70)
    - Ariana Reines, undated (Box 70)
    - Joan Retallack, undated (Box 70)
    - Donald Revell, undated (Box 70)
    - Mariana Rexroth, undated (Box 70)
    - Barbara Jane Reyes, undated (Box 70)
    - Christopher Rice, undated (Box 70)
    - Doug Rice, undated (Box 70)
    - Adrienne Rich, undated (Box 70)
    - Deborah Richards, undated (Box 70)
    - Patti Richman, undated (Box 70)
    - Kieran Ridge, undated (Box 70)
    - Kota Uetsu and Okichuu at opening of Right Window gallery, undated (Box 70)
    - Fake painting at Right Window (Kevin, Karla, Cadence, Colter, Sept 2008), 2008 September (Box 70)
    - Blake Riley, undated (Box 70)
    - Bridget Riley, undated (Box 70)
    - Larry Rinder, undated (Box 70)
    - Larry Rinder with Red Strings, undated (Box 70)
    - Alberto Rios, undated (Box 70)
    - Vince Roark, undated (Box 70)
    - Rob Roberge, undated (Box 70)
    - Adreana Robbins, undated (Box 70)
    - Micah Robbins, undated (Box 70)
    - Ed Roberson, undated (Box 70)
    - Larry-bob, Laurence Roberts ·, undated (Box 70)
    - Lisa Robertson, undated (Box 70)
    - Lisa Robertson in a mask, undated (Box 70)
    - Elizabeth Robinson, undated (Box 70)
    - Jeffrey Robinson, undated (Box 70)
    - Kit Robinson, undated (Box 70)
    - Sophie Robinson, undated (Box 70)
    - Stephen Rodefer, undated (Box 70)
    - Eric Rodriguez with Burgher sigil applied to torso (photographer unknown), undated (Box 70)
    - Joao Pedro Rodriguez, undated (Box 70)
    - Matt Rohrer, Goetry!, undated (Box 70)
    - Martha Ronk, undated (Box 70)
    - Rooftop of auto body shop, undated (Box 70)
    - Sheree Rose, undated (Box 70)
    - White Roses at kari edwards' memorial, December 13, 2006, 2006 December 13 (Box 70)
    - Red and pink roses, September 2010, 2010 September (Box 70)
    - Jerry Rosen, undated (Box 70)
    - Oliver Halsman Rosenberg, undated (Box 70)
    - Kim Rosenfield, undated (Box 70)
    - Phyllis Rosenzweig, undated (Box 70)
    - Martha Rosler, undated (Box 70)
    - Matthue Roth, undated (Box 70)
    - Jerome Rothenberg, undated (Box 70)
    - Josh Rothenberg, the assistant to Chris Felver, undated (Box 70)
    - Michael Rothenberg, undated (Box 70)
    - Doug Rothschild, undated (Box 70)
    - Doug Rothschild, undated (Box 70)
    - Emily Roysdon, undated (Box 70)
    - Ralph Rugoff, undated (Box 70)
    - Aida Ruilova and Kevin Killian, China Art, undated (Box 70)
    - Objects, Christmas 2009, 2009 December 25 (Box 70)
    - Conrad Ruiz, undated (Box 70)
    - David Rumsey, undated (Box 70)
    - Christopher Russell, undated (Box 70)
    - Jane Russell, undated (Box 70)
    - John Russell, undated (Box 70)
    - Jocelyn Saidenberg as "Connie Moorman", undated (Box 70)
    - Jocelyn Saidenberg rehearsing "The Shakers", undated (Box 70)
    - Cynthia Sailers, undated (Box 70)
    - James Saint James, undated (Box 70)
    - Angelos Sakkis, undated (Box 70)
    - Ashley Lauren Saks, undated (Box 70)
    - Jerome Sala, undated (Box 70)
    - Steve Salardino, undated (Box 70)
    - Mark Salemo, undated (Box 70)
    - Arno Salters, undated (Box 70)
    - Canyon Sam, undated (Box 70)
    - Lisa Samuels, undated (Box 70)
    - Sonia Sanchez, undated (Box 70)
    - Kaia Sand, undated (Box 70)
    - Jay Sanders, undated (Box 70)
    - Santa with Butt Plug, by Paul McCarthy, Art Basel 38, undated (Box 70)
    - Tura Satana, undated (Box 70)
    - Jennifer Scappettone and Keith Boadwee, undated (Box 74)
    - Marie-Celine Schaefer, undated (Box 70)
    - Ingrid Schaffner, undated (Box 70)
    - Michael Scharf, undated (Box 70)
    - Kate Schatz, undated (Box 70)
    - Stephanie Schiff, undated (Box 70)
    - Kyle Schlesinger, undated (Box 70)
    - Zachary Royer Scholz, undated (Box 70)
    - Carly Schorman and Lucas Rivera, undated (Box 70)
    - Sarah Schulman, undated (Box 70)
    - Sarah Schulman and Mona de Vestal, undated (Box 70)
    - Kathy Lou Schultz, undated (Box 70)
    - Susan M. Schultz, undated (Box 70)
    - Joshua Schuster, undated (Box 70)
    - Barry Schwabsky, undated (Box 70)
    - Jenny Scobel, undated (Box 70)
    - Gail Scott, undated (Box 70)
    - Jordan Scott's ass, undated (Box 70)
    - Kathryn Leigh Scott, undated (Box 70)
    - D. Travers Scott, undated (Box 70)
    - Ramsey Scott, undated (Box 70)
    - John Searles, undated (Box 70)
    - Steven Seidenberg, undated (Box 71)
    - Lasana M. Sekou, undated (Box 71)
    - Will Self, undated (Box 71)
    - Peter Selz, undated (Box 71)
    - Ascension Serrano, undated (Box 71)
    - Shakers rehearsals, June 2000, 2000 June (Box 71)
    - Todd Shalom, undated (Box 71)
    - Jack Shamama, undated (Box 71)
    - David Shapiro, undated (Box 71)
    - Harvey Shapiro, undated (Box 71)
    - Prageeta Sharma, undated (Box 71)
    - Steven Shaviro, undated (Box 71)
    - Jim Shaw, undated (Box 71)
    - Lytle Shaw, undated (Box 71)
    - Frank Sherlock, undated (Box 71)
    - Christine Shields, undated (Box 71)
    - Reed Shier, undated (Box 71)
    - Ara Shirinyan, undated (Box 71)
    - Evie Shockley, undated (Box 71)
    - Shower Tile in Mike and Donald's bathroom, undated (Box 71)
    - Leslie Shows, undated (Box 71)
    - Nathaniel Siegel, undated (Box 71)
    - West Siegmiller, undated (Box 71)
    - Christian Siekmeier, undated (Box 71)
    - Cedar Sigo and Johnny Ray Huston, undated (Box 71)
    - Cedar Sigo and his mother Lynne Ferguson, undated (Box 71)
    - Michael Sikkema, undated (Box 71)
    - Susan Silton, undated (Box 71)
    - Sally Silvers, undated (Box 71)
    - Steven Simmons, undated (Box 71)
    - Sandra Simonds and fiance Craig, undated (Box 71)
    - Laura Sims, undated (Box 71)
    - Bucky Sinister, undated (Box 71)
    - Justin Sirois, undated (Box 71)
    - Sisters of Perpetual Indulgence, undated (Box 71)
    - Dieta Sixt, undated (Box 71)
    - Thomas Skidmore, undated (Box 71)
    - Jonathan Skinner, undated (Box 71)
    - Eric Slade, undated (Box 71)
    - Davida Small, undated (Box 71)
    - Frank Smigiel, undated (Box 71)